good morning and here are your top five
stocks to watch out for and trade today
well plenty of numbers that will be
declared today and among the lot you've
got kotak Bank SBI live torent Pharma
and &m financial a quick snapshot as to
what to expect from kotak bank today
you've got the nii which is expected at
3,780 CR versus 3724 QQ Pat seen at,
1600 cres the loan growth could improve
sequentially Nims could remain steady
you are expecting low credit cost
expectations possibly 150 and 150 to 160
basis points and uh Provisions could
remain
elevated getting a move on then let's
focus in on earnings that came out on
Friday and over the weekend you had icci
Lombard which declared its numbers where
the pat came in at 415 crores versus 30
OR7 CR rupees you had the combined ratio
which stood at
9.7% versus
10.6% the solvency ratio standing at
about .47 times as on September 30th
capital gain stood at 120 cres versus 69
CR y why Tech Mahindra then that's
another result candidate to watch out
for the dollar revenue is coming in at
$165 million up about 4.8% sequentially
Revenue growth came in a
9,372 crores up 2.9% on aq1 Q basis the
ebit at about 1331 cror up 45% sequ
eventually with the a bit margin
standing at a healthy 14.2% versus
10.1% their new deal win stood at about
$421 million well Morgan Stanley says
that they maintain an overweight rating
on Tech Mahindra with a Target price at
980 seeing the strong margin Improvement
continues Revenue was slightly better
than estimates and the margin expansion
was significantly better they say that M
management sees the growth Outlook
improving in
fy22 yes Bank meim came out with its
earnings with a pat at 129 crores versus
a loss of 600 crores last year nii at
1973 cres Provisions came in at 1187
crores versus 1336 crores y y the asset
quality improved to 16.9% versus 17.3%
on the gnps and net NPS at
4.71% versus
4.96% and Nestle came out with its
earnings revenues up 10% 571 CR for Q3
the path stood at 587 CR which was
flattish lower by 1% margins grew 115
basis points to come in at 24.95 per.
they said that there's been double digit
growth in their key Brands and that's
been boosted by the inh Home consumption
reversal in the tax of the base quarter
impacted the pat there's been strong
performance in the E channels which has
grown nearly
97% clsa has upgraded the stock to
outperform from sell with a Target at uh
17650 saying that the concerns are
fading and normaly will Aid going
forward